Enzo Cazenave

enzocazenavedev@hotmail.com | +54 11 4528 0608 | Buenos Aires, Argentina. | https://cazenave.online

ABOUT ME

I enjoy creating things that live on the internet. Currently a happy computer engineering student, who is always dedicated to perfecting his skills and addressing various challenges.

In addition to my passion for being constantly growing, I enjoy my hobbies in my free time. I have been a field hockey player since i was 4 year old. Also, i love riding ATV. My hobbies are a way for me to relax and disconnect from routine.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Engineer

Jun 2023 - Present

Upbrands Agency, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Specialized in creating impressive and functional web interfaces.
- Effective collaboration with teams to transform creative concepts into high-quality, high-performance web solutions.

Freelance Developer

Jan 2022 - Dec 2022

Freelancing from Buenos Aires, Argentina.

• I developed FiveM game server scripts, functionalities and interfaces for international clients, standing out for my ability to create unique and engaging gaming experiences.

PROJECTS

Inmunes Roleplay

Jan 2020 - Dec 2021

Lua, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, MySQL

I led the development and management of Inmunes RP, a FiveM server that reached a daily average of more than 200 simultaneous players, standing out for its stability and immersive gaming experience. I achieved self-sustainability of the server by implementing an internal store, providing benefits to users and contributing to the continuous growth of Inmunes RP.

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering

Jan 2022 - Present

Universidad Argentina de la Empresa (UADE), Montserrat, BA.

Higher diploma in English training

Brighton English Institute, Berazategui, BA.

Jan 2011 - Dec 2021

COURSES

Electron & React: Creating desktop app's. Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

Udemy (Online Learning Platform)

React Native: Native app's for IOS and Android. Sep 2022 - Jan 2023

Udemy (Online Learning Platform)

React: Real time app's with socket-io. Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

Udemy (Online Learning Platform)

React & MERN: Web Development Feb 2022 - Aug 2022

Udemy (Online Learning Platform)

PHP and the Web. Sep 2020 - Jan 2021

Mastermind (Online Learning Platform)

Learn to program with Python. Feb 2020 - Apr 2020

Mastermind (Online Learning Platform)